whatbird.com 2018-10-08

# WhatBird Privacy Policy

**Information about our Organization and Web site Privacy Policy**

Modern information and communication technologies play a fundamental role in the activities of an Organization like Mitch Waite Group. We are based in United States. Our principal activities are: Software sales. Our privacy policy covers Mitch Waite Group and its Web site: 

| 

Web site: 

| 

www.whatbird.com   
  
---|---  
  
Organization Name:

| 

Mitch Waite Group   
  
Address: 

| 

3001 Bridgeway  
  
Address: 

| 

Suite K-321  
  
City, Zip: 

| 

Sausalito, 94965   
  
State: 

| 

CA   
  
Country: 

| 

United States   
  
Controller: 

| 

Mitchell Waite   
  
Telephone | 415 888 3233   
  
**Providing Visitors with Anonymous Access**  
You can access our Web site home page and browse our site without disclosing your personal data. 

**The services and links of our Web site**   
Our Web site enables you to communicate with other visitors or to post information to be accessed by others. When you do so, other visitors may collect your data. Our Web site does not include links to third party Web service providers. 

**Automatic Collection of Information**   
We do not automatically log personal data nor do we link information automatically logged by other means with personal data about specific individuals. We do not use cookies to store personal data nor do we link non-personal information stored in cookies with personal data about specific individuals. We do collect hit usage in our server logs. This may include the IP address of your web provider. 

**Data Collection and Purpose Specification**   
We do not collect any personal data from our visitors when they use our services. We do not collect information about our visitors from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private Organizations. 

**Privacy Compliance**  
There are no national laws or self-regulatory schemes applicable to our web site or Organization. There are no global or regional regulatory or self-regulatory schemes applicable to our web site or Organization.

**Privacy Support**  
If you have an enquiry or concern about our privacy policy, please contact us at the above address.
